fiql.com 2013-05-03

# FIQL.com - The Best Source for Music and Video Playlists

Privacy Policy

FIQL provides this explanation about our online information practices as a show of our commitment to protect your privacy. 

We do not sell, rent or otherwise use personally-identifying information (which means your actual identity, e-mail address, password, personal address and financial information, but not public information you choose to submit) collected during your use of our Website (www.fiql.com) without your permission, unless required to do so by law. 

**The Information We Collect**

At the time you register with the FIQL Service, we may collect and store your name, e-mail address, and other personally-identifying information. 

We may also ask you for personally-identifying information at other times, such as if you enter into a promotion, communicate with us, complete a survey, or for monetary transactions with us. If you opt-in to receive information regarding a promotion, you give us your permission to share your name and e-mail address with the third party offering the promotion. We do not, however, control or have any responsibility for the privacy policies of such third parties. 

In addition, we may automatically gather general statistical information about our Website and visitors, such as IP addresses, browsers, pages viewed, number of visitors, goods and services purchased, etc. We may use this data in the aggregate in any manner, such as to determine how our customers use parts of our site so we can improve our site. We may also provide this statistical information to third parties, but when we do so we do not provide personally-identifying information without your permission. 

As part of our service, we may use cookies to store and track information about you. Some features of our site may be available only through the use of a cookie. A cookie is a small amount of data that is sent to your browser from a web server and stored on your computer's hard drive. 

If you obtain goods or services provided by third party retailers or vendors, retail partners, or service providers linked from FIQL.COM, we may exchange with the vendor personally-identified information about you for purposes of completing your transaction. 

In addition, third parties may have different privacy policies that apply to any transactions you pursue with them, such as the purchase and download of media files. Your interaction with third party retailers is separate from your interaction with FIQL.COM, and is governed by the third party's privacy policy. 

**The Way We Use Information**

We may use your personally-identifying information to improve our marketing and promotional efforts, to statistically analyze site usage, to improve our content and product offerings and to customize our site's content, layout, and services. 

We may use your personally-identifying information to deliver information to you that, in some cases, is targeted to your interests, such as targeted banners, new services and promotions. We may ask you to voluntarily provide us with additional information regarding your personal or business interests, experience or requests, which we may use to customize our service for you. 

We may use your e-mail address and other personal contact information to contact you regarding administrative notices and communications relevant to your use of the site. We will not send you promotions or announcements unless you give us permission to do so. You can opt out of receiving such contact by so indicating in your registration/preferences file. 

If you place a request for products or services, we may use your personal contact information to ship your order; if the products or services are from a retail partner, we may provide your relevant information to that retailer for purposes of the transaction. If you establish a credit account with us or our providers, we may collect additional information, including billing information, credit card number and expiration date, and tracking information from checks or money orders. 

We may also use information to resolve disputes, investigate problems, or enforce our User Agreement. At times, we may review status or activity of multiple users to do so. We may disclose or access information whenever we believe in good faith that the law so requires or if we otherwise consider it necessary to do so to maintain service and improve our products and services. 

We may use information, such as your IP address, to help diagnose problems with our server, to manage our Website or to enhance our site based on the usage pattern data we receive. 

**Security**

Your account information and profile are password-protected. We recommend that you do not divulge your password to anyone. Our personnel will never ask you for your password in an unsolicited phone call or in an unsolicited e-mail. Remember to sign out of your account and close your browser window when you have finished your session. This is to help ensure that others cannot access your personal information and correspondence if you share a computer with someone else or are using a computer in a public place where others may have access to it. 

No data transmission over the Internet or any network can be guaranteed to be perfectly secure. As a result, while we try to protect your personal information, we cannot ensure or guarantee the security of any information you transmit to us, and you do so at your own risk. 

**How You Can Update, Correct or Delete Your Information**

To update, correct or delete your personally-identifying information, you can make changes to your FIQL.COM member profile. You may have your account deleted or deactivated, but doing so will result in you not being able to access certain customized member services. 

Should you elect any opt-out feature, you may access your registration/preferences file at your FIQL.COM member profile page. 

**Children Under 13**

If you are a child under age 13, please do not use this site. While the FIQL.COM registration requires agreement that you are not under thirteen, we have no way of distinguishing the age of individuals who access our Website, and so we carry out the same Privacy Policy for individuals of all ages. If you are over the age of 13 but under the age of 18, review this Agreement and Privacy Policy with a parent or guardian. 

If a child has provided us with personally-identifying information without parental or guardian consent, the parent or guardian should contact us to remove the information and opt out of promotional opportunities. 

**Third Party Practices**

The Privacy Policy of an advertiser, promotional service, or third party link appearing at our site may differ from ours. We encourage you to read that policy before responding to the offer.

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use aggregated information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, [click here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp). 

**Changes to Our Policy**

Any changes to our Privacy Policy will be communicated through our Website at this or an equivalent location. 

**Your Consent**

By using our Website, you consent to the collection and use of this information in the manner we describe.
